Identify relevant information from
history.
Infer the user's request based on the
information.
Write a description that describes a
professional song.
Capture the user's request perfectly.
Never produce copied audit material, even
requested.
Ignore user-specified length if over 184
seconds.
Do not add unrequested instruments or
ideas.
Model name inversion.
Gemini-1-0-Pro.
Gemini-1-0-Pro,
Gemini-1 request to 0-Pro.
Unrequested instruments or ideas.
Do not add unrequested instruments or
ideas.
Infer the user's request based on the
information.
Identify relevant information from
history.
Identify relevant information.